this is the car now Takara was here six
months ago
to reveal a painful secret to her
boyfriend Jason and her sister Brittany
take a look at her last appearance
when we first met Takara she was
overcome with emotion and desperate to
get the truth out my sister really means
a lot to me I've been keeping a secure
floor here and it's really hurt me I
know they said he's like where's my
sister
I was taking away with Raymond for a
year
the rest of the secrets you know I'm
pregnant
oh my
God she's screaming Britney I'm sorry
baby
Takara also had to tell her own
boyfriend Jason
for a year
if you all come back we'll do a
paternity test today Takara Raymond and
Jason will finally find out the DNA
truth
so finally we're going to have an ending
to this very painful story because now
there's a little girl five-month-old
Amaya and there she is
[Applause]
but who's the father
the cousins are back Raymond and Jason
and we've given everybody a paternity
test we're going to have the results a
little later but first your sister is
here Brittany is here hi Brittany hello
welcome back
now Britain
is there any possibility of you all
getting closer I mean we've been working
on it before I told her like we can try
to put the relationship back together
but I still ain't nobody to trust her
it's gonna be hard it's gonna be hard
for me to trust her again because okay I
mean it was going on for too long in my
house and I mean it was going it was it
was crazy so both these guys are out of
your lives yes well um since my baby's
been born Jason Jason he ain't done
nothing for my baby Jason has it no your
ex-boyfriend has done nothing Well
Raymond his cousin he's actually bought
my baby diapers clothes formula he's
like
thank you
so Raymond right the guy you slept with
yes your sister's ex fiance at the time
he's been the one who's taking care of
the baby yes wow so you want him to be
the baby's father I know that's my
sister's ex-fiance say they have kids
together but I see that gosh you have
kids
you all have kids how many four four
oh
wow a little bit
this is hard
you don't know whether Amaya is is a
sister to those other kids or not you
just don't know cousin or sister one of
the two
I'm just I'm just ready to get the
results so I can get to the bottom of
this because I love my sister and Ray is
nothing it's nothing well we might as
well hear from the two cousins Jason and
Raymond this is what they had to say
before it's been six months since the
show uh Takara had her baby and I do not
think I'm the father Takara cheated on
me with my cousin and she cheated on me
with my cousin who knows who else she
cheated on me with I know there's a 50
chance that this baby might be mine but
I hope it's not because it'll make
everything complicated I haven't been
there for Takara because I don't think
that's my baby I try to be there as much
as I can for the baby but it's been hard
with all the drama that's been going on
honestly I hope the child is not mine
because me and the car don't even kick
it like that no more if the baby is mine
I will step up a man up and uh take care
of my responsibilities I don't want a
relationship with Takara I want to work
things out with her sister Brittany
because I still love her but if this is
my baby I don't know if me and Brittany
will be able to move forward
not really we ain't him being together I
don't think he'll work because no matter
what I can't trust him I can't trust him
here are Jason and Raymond here they are
how you doing Brandon good to see you
nice to see you again Jason nice to see
you and welcome back nice to see you
Raymond
you're kind of stepping up with that
young lady aren't you sir how come
I mean
somebody got to be the father and the
baby needs things done for us so
I'm gonna try to do what I can do how
come you don't want anything to do with
that little baby I mean I ain't nothing
I ain't gotta want to do or do with the
babies just I don't want to do with her
so once we find out who the father is
then you would step up Jason right yeah
no problem well guess what we're gonna
have the results right now
foreign
[Applause]
Jason
you are not the father
[Applause]
and in the case of five-month-old Amaya
Raymond you are not
[Applause]
yeah
come on
[Applause]
come on it's gonna be okay
we'll be glad to help you if you want us
to find the father we will Takara okay
now your sister's here Brittany this is
a time he needs her sister okay
you know something they're one there's
one good thing that could come out of
this right Brittany you could be close
again to your sister because she needs
you right here okay everyone this is
Keisha welcome Keisha to the show
and
and backstage
backstage is Keisha's boyfriend Mario
now this is Keisha and Mario's
one-year-old son Trenton
as you can see
baby Trenton is very light complexity
Keisha says the color of Trenton's skin
has destroyed her and Mario's family and
she's desperate for a paternity test
because Mario believes that Trenton is
too white to be his son and wants him
Mario is the love of my life
mistake that I have made could cost my
entire future with him Mario does not
believe that he's the father of our
one-year-old son Trenton but I'm 100
sure to hear
I did cheat on Mario one time but I was
already pregnant when it happened
Trenton looks just like my
three-year-old son that I have with
Mario even Mario's Family agrees with
that the man that I want to marry has no
trust in me but I refuse to let him keep
denying that treating his hands I'm
going to prove that Trenton has Mario's
DNA running all through his bank and
when I do all his BS needs to end
immediately
you're angry yes I'm actually Furious
why because just because my son has a
light skin complexion don't mean you got
every right to go around and deny my
child you're not gonna know it
but here's the problem Keisha you did
make a mistake around the time you got
pregnant I made a mistake but I was
already pregnant when I went to the
doctor I found out I was seven weeks
pregnant does Mario believe that no he
don't
Mario says that child's too late to be
his how about that look at them you
think they look alike
it's not my babies
[Applause]
my baby is awesome
wait a second
you all have another child together you
have a three-year-old yes now do they
look alike yeah huh yes they do but you
know what I heard I heard Mario spends
more more time with the three-year-old
than he does Trenton he does
right
the other gotta go get it oh
[Applause]
this is what Mario had to say watch I'm
black my girlfriend Keisha is black but
the baby she's saying is mine he looks
white when Keisha was six months
pregnant she admitted she cheated on me
she said it happened around the time she
got pregnant but she swears Trenton is
my son I want to believe Trenton was my
son what gives me hope is that Trenton
look like my other son by Keisha I cried
over this I can't stand the thought of
Trenton being another man's son my
family is my whole world I'm never going
to stop loving training my heart would
be crushed if I find out today that I'm
not his father
but you heard what Mario said I'm black
my girlfriend's black and my child is
white here's Mario come on out
[Applause]
you all are still together don't put
that thing over there he should open his
chair over there you two are still
together you're a family he takes care
of your three-year-old you have another
child and him
but I get to feeling Mario the state of
your relationship has really suffered
right yes you have how come because she
cheated on me and she said this I mean
what are you cheating on me I ain't
never cheated on you and didn't look at
his skin complexion look at him
look at me
you know I read that your family thinks
that it's that it's yours yes they do
think Trenton is mine really do if he's
not my child he's going to treat him
like I've been treating him
gonna be there for you are you going to
go out for milk yes you have to get milk
out for milk okay all right well we're
gonna find out right now
when it comes to one-year-old Trenton
Mario
you are not
[Applause]
sure
this is your man you you share a child
he would be a father to this child
he said he would be a father to this
child
okay
all right
he's not the father he's not the birth
father but he's there every single day
okay
right
Mario
this is very painful for her okay
if you have any feeling for her
you will be a father to this child
foreign
she can't write off what happened what
happened happened you know you can't not
think about it but at the same time you
can move on
you can be a family together you share
another child he knew he is going to
move on okay good for you I'm glad
everyone this is Tiandra Welcome To
Yonder
how
deondra admits
DeAndre admits when she was 15 years old
she was kind of out of control and she
was headed down a dangerous path
but today her past catches up with her
because Tiandra has a four-year-old son
named travion
how cute he is
and she is not sure who the father is
you see Tiandra believes her
ex-boyfriend Vincent is the dad
but it could also be her current
boyfriend Andre
or a third man named John
[Applause]
but you're more positive that it's
Vincent than the other two yes Mari
everybody's got to understand the story
all right yes when I was 15 like I said
I was a little wow I did things I regret
and now that I'm older I see the mistake
that I've made yes
but
who do you want to be the fox Andre he's
been there with me the whole four years
he was at the hospital
it really helped me he's been there with
me the whole time but you think of
expensive yeah has Vincent done anything
for Travian
we haven't seen him in almost four years
who does this lovely boy look like
here's Vincent
here's Andre here's John
we might as well hear from the guys all
right here's what they had to say about
the situation three men
one baby and a DNA mystery Vincent
tiandra's ex-boyfriend is convinced
there's no way he's the father when me
and Santa together she cheated on me and
she played and what I got cheat on me
with with my best friend Andre and
that's who I believe is the father of
her baby but Andre tiandra's current
boyfriend has a different story I'm the
one who's been taking care of trayvion
since the day he was born I wish he was
mine but today set up to Vincent as the
father for John this situation has left
him clueless I don't have any kids so to
find out I might have a four-year-old is
very surprising I honestly don't know
how to feel about the situation one
thing is certain the truth must come out
let's hurry up with these results
because the baby's not mine I love this
little boy so much but we need to get to
the bottom of these fraternity results
Travian needs to know which one of the
three of us is his father
here they are Vincent Andre and John
welcome
John thanks very much
John
I think that child looks like you
because I'm talking to you first because
you're the least to do with this I mean
you're kind of like an add-on in the
lips a little bit in the lips a little
bit just a little bit but okay Vincent
you all were together right yeah what
happened
that's not me that's not mine it's not
yours boy it's not mine why can't you
just have your responsibility
[Applause]
no no here's the deal this is what I'm
getting from you Andre yeah you don't
think it's yours but you want it to be
yours I mean I want it to be mad because
I was there
like I feel like I feel like more
responsibility
you wouldn't even knowing this kid why
not step up because you know my father
wasn't there when I was little and I
don't want to see I want to see a little
check go out like that man be innocent
man
I can't just leave here by myself
this is what I don't understand why I
can't more men think like this
see a lot of guys think that they're
saddled with a child
you think of it as a joy it's a blessing
just to have one but if you got one of
you not there it don't make sense that
don't make sense does that get through
to you Vincent I hope it do
Vincent if this is your child you I'm
gonna take care of it yeah I'm gonna
take care of it and I'm sure you would
John although John
I'm not too sure why you're here so we
we might as well have the results
thank you
when it comes to four-year-old travion
remember we're not talking about an
infant now
this is a four-year-old child John
you are not the father
that comes the four-year-old travion
Andre
you are not the father
and when it comes to four-year-old
trevion Vincent
you are not
oh
my God
oh my God oh my God I don't want to be
back here
stop stop stop that's okay it's okay
[Music]
look at me man look at me I ain't going
nowhere man I love you man I love you
too
I love you so much Andre
you are great because I know you're
going to be a father to this job
man let's take a look at one and a half
year old Hannah now she she is truly a
miracle baby because Hannah was born
premature
how about this one everybody when she
was born she weighed one pound nine
ounces
this is Pam Hannah the mother
and when Pam looks at her incredible
daughter she is filled with both
happiness and despair you see Pam isn't
sure if her husband Chris is Hannah's
father
before Pam got pregnant with Hannah she
and Chris had briefly broken up and it
was during that time when Pam was
intimate I think one time or more than
one time
one time with another man we've given
Chris a paternity test before we reveal
the results listen to how the situation
has affected Pam and her marriage to
Chris
my husband Chris and I are so in love
everything in my relationship is so
perfect
except I wanted to have your
[Music]
half your card since I love
them ease my heart and soul
a few years ago I made the worst mistake
of my life I slept with an ex-boyfriend
no I don't know
[Music]
we call Hannah our miracle baby
born at 25 weeks
one pound I can't have any more children
and it breaks my heart to know
I can't give Chris another baby
Hannah isn't it
I'm so scared that Chris will leave
his daughter
and my heart will be broken forever
but you love Chris
I love him
and he loves you yes and what does he
say about the possibility if he's not
the father
what does he say
he said that he still wants to be with
me
you know I just feel you don't believe
him I feel like
he's gonna leave me
but think about what you all have been
through this is a miracle child one
pound nine ounces yes
so hard
[Music]
I've been with him I've had some
surgeries and stuff and it's been so
hard for us he's been oral and you can't
have any more children I can't have any
more they cut burn and ties you think
Hannah and Chris look alike I do this is
what Chris had to say before the show
I'm here today to find out if my one and
a half year old daughter is really my
child or not I love Hannah with all my
heart one week after Pam had told me
that she was pregnant she told me that
the baby that we were expecting may not
be mine
Hannah is my world I would be devastated
if I wasn't her father in my heart I do
believe that Hannah is mine but there is
that doubt for the past two years I've
tried to block these feelings out of my
mind I can't eat I can't sleep it's
ruining my life it hurts so much to
think about Hannah not being mine I'm
praying the guy that these results come
back to Anna is my daughter if they
don't I'm going to be very crushed the
whole world would never be the same
again
here's Chris Chris come on out
[Music]
she's afraid you'll leave
he's afraid you'll leave I'm not going
nowhere if you're going to be there no
matter what why do we need the test
we just to ease my mind knowing that she
is my biological daughter
you think she looks like you I'm gonna
ask you one more time what's gonna
happen if you're not her biological
father I'm going to be here regardless
whether she come out or not
[Applause]
I just don't want you to say no
when it comes to one and a half year old
Hannah Chris you are not
[Applause]
[Music]
good
[Applause]
[Music]
okay everybody I want to ask you
something
did you ever break up with somebody
and then have
one more night of passion before
well
that's what happened to our next guest
Janice and her ex-boyfriend Tom welcome
Janice to the show
see
shortly after they split up Janice had
one more night of passion
and now she claims that night resulted
in her getting pregnant with her now
five-month-old son Xavier
Tom
he has a completely different story all
of her talk is just the ploy to get him
back and the baby Xavier is not his son
oh yes this is Tom's side of the story
my ex-girlfriend Janice is a disgusting
liar and a desperate nag she would do
anything to make me believe I'm the
father of her son Xavier but I know I'm
not
if you wrote down all the guys Jan it's
been what you would have Pages pages and
pages
Janice knows I got kids that I already
take care she just wants that for her
kid Xavier I can't help with the other
guys that she slept with are losers I
don't think Xavier looks anything like
me I feel zero connection to this boy
Dennis stalks me it's obvious she has
feelings for me she's just jealous I'm
back with my ex she's trying to use her
baby to get me back in her life good
luck finding your son's father you're
gonna need it
[Applause]
all right
pages and Pages time right right okay
what's the truth the truth is is we went
to the short last July he begged me
while he was with him he still said oh I
still get to go on that vacation with
you and your family right yeah sure I
brought him with me and then you made it
with him yeah we got drunk and we wound
up doing the nasty
no no no no no no
not at all no no
it ain't mine it's not mine I don't even
hear you you I'm talking to Mari not you
yes yes
congratulations
[Applause]
Tom did I do it right you had another
night of passion after you broke up and
therefore yeah we didn't yeah we
definitely did so why is it okay no no
it was a couple nights yeah down the
shore yeah
what happened a week before we went to
shore huh whatever the week after we
came home from sure how many guys three
three three three times
[Applause]
if he's mine look at that though I don't
see no resemblance except for blue eyes
a baby can come out with blue eyes
we're gonna find out right now
foreign
Xavier you are the Father Tom you are
not
[Applause]
here
don't leave Jan Jan don't leave use what
you put me through put me through this
you better go check them other people
not me cannot an apology can I get an
apology
I'm sorry but y'all Tom yo you oh my god
yo oh my God okay oh my God you almost
ruined my life
okay my baby you're my baby I don't care
who the father is taking care of him
I'll take care of my baby
hey everyone this is Kayla welcome Kayla
all right now
this was a storybook relationship a prom
picture of Kayla and her husband Seth
they were a young couple in high school
in fact she was the cheerleader he was
the star football player
and after graduation they got married
and then as it happens there was a brief
separation
and Kayla made a horrible mistake
because she's not sure if Seth is the
father of her five-month-old daughter
Paisley watch
I was 14 years old
I met Seth I was a cheerleader and he
was a football player he was my best
friend he's my everything and I love him
my wedding day was it was just me and
him standing there he was just so
sincere
losing that would be really really hard
I was wrong for stepping outside of my
marriage and I would never
never doing
Seth is the most amazing father and when
I look at my daughter
I want her to know who her daddy is
I feel guilty because this could change
her life forever she loves her daddy I
just pray the results come back that
he's the father and we can go home
and we can start over
look at that
what a great looking picture but we
never think to me you have no clue
you're afraid he might walk away now
you don't know I don't know this is what
Seth had to say emotionally this is the
hardest thing I've ever been through
Kayla means the world to me she's the
only girl I've ever been with going
through that separation was very
heart-wrenching um
she's
I'm sorry
it destroyed me I just prayed every day
she'd be back
I can't imagine not having Caleb Paisley
and Elijah I just want us all together
it hurts me a lot thinking about
that's not being a family and being
together because I got pregnant I know
either way that little girl needed me
I'm just hoping in the end that she
would be mine if I was not crazy father
I'm sorry
I will do my best to be her father as
long as I'm allowed to be there and
she's not ripped away from me I feel
like if I could make it through this you
know we can make it through anything
okay
according to Kayla this is the best man
in the world here's Seth everybody
for me are you doing
okay
Seth you know what her fear is
that this is not your child you'll walk
away you know I'll always be there you
will
you're prepared for this I think Casey
looks like you yes I do yeah let's just
like me I believe I believe you when you
say that you will be there and that you
will remain a family no matter what the
result is no matter what
what's up to me
in the case of five-month-old Paisley
Seth you are not
[Applause]
um
oh
my God oh my God
[Music]
oh my God
happened
okay it's gonna be all right everyone
this is Tara welcome Tara
now
apparently this is happening more and
more in this country Tara meets a man
Sean on the internet
they make an instant connection
the bond was so strong that Sean
literally walked 250 miles to meet Tara
for the first time
but as fast as he walked into her life
he walked out
because a month later Tara got pregnant
and Sean abandoned her
so now Tara has a three-month-old son
named Braden and Sean has never even met
you think they look alike
I think he has Sean's eye color but I
think he looks like my son that passed
away
so after you after he walked how long
did you all stay together
for about a month about a month and then
I found that I was pregnant yes what did
he do he was happy at first and then
people started telling him I cheated you
are I did cheat on me
come on you know you cheated don't lie
about it has he ever seen Braden no
never this is what Sean told my
producers I walked 250 miles to meet
that woman but what I walked into is not
what I expected we went to a club one
night she was on the dance floor making
out with another guy I think she was
cheating with other guys the whole time
I had people telling me she slept with
seven other men one of my friends told
me straight up that he had sex with her
Sarah also got pregnant awfully fast I
mean come on this baby could be anybody
come on out
I love you
[Applause]
like me and blue eyes Sean wait a second
let's get this straight you wanted to
come to meet her right yes how did you
walk 250 miles in two days
sometimes we'll give you a ride
sometimes you think you look like
Brayden no sir I don't I don't think I
looked anything like him let's find out
okay
foreign
when it comes to three-month-old Brayden
Sean
you are not
[Applause]
oh my God everyone this is Aisha welcome
Aisha
now
this is for all you teenagers
because Aisha is 18 years old
she enjoyed being a cheerleader she
enjoyed tutoring her other classmates
and then all of a sudden at 17 she turns
up pregnant
with her now three-month-old daughter
Christiana
now Aisha
has been overwhelmed by the sheer
responsibility of raising a baby the
alleged father Diamond has completely
abandoned them
[Applause]
I thought he was honest and caring and
really cared about me but when I found
out I was pregnant he had lied to me at
first and said he wore a condom which he
did but he had took it off and he lied
to me about it he hasn't done anything
for my baby I asked him to get his baby
some formula and he told me no it's
because of him that she's here she
didn't ask to be born she had to be put
here on this Earth all I want is for him
to be a part of christiana's life
because I grew up without a father and I
know what it's like she shouldn't have
to go through that by herself
thing notices baby I don't understand I
don't ask him to take off the economy oh
you didn't even know no I didn't at
first until I went to the hospital and
they told me I was ready that's when I
found out then he told you that he told
you he took them because he did but he
didn't accept responsibility no he did
not and it made me very upset like how
could you do that to me when you know
you know what you did you know you're
the father my daughter deserves to have
both of her parents and her life
foreign
[Applause]
you never expected to be on this show
I didn't I never expected to be here
because I thought he was gonna own up
and take responsibility of his baby but
you didn't expect to even be in the
position of being pregnant no not at 17.
I don't regret my baby I love my baby
but I just wish that I would have got
pregnant at a later time because I
wanted to feel would you tell all those
teenagers out there to stop thinking
about getting yes I would tell you
that's right the ways to get pregnant
wait for everything wait to have sex all
of it you were a big student yeah I was
I was in volleyball cheerleading I was
in math relay I told the other students
I love school schools important to me I
wanted to finish school I wanted to get
my diploma and now I have to settle for
a GED instead that's the only way you're
going to get it is a GED yeah you know
what he says he throws a lot of rumors
around about you I know who I am as a
person I know what I do he can't tell me
foreign
yes he came to the hospital stay tonight
and then the next day after the baby was
born and I'm in the hospital he gonna
say he wanted DNA test he wanted to be
sure I'd have asked him to take off the
condom I would have never got pregnant
in the first place
this is what Simon had to say what I was
only trying to be friends with Aisha
nothing more than that we only had sex
one time when she said she was pregnant
I knew she was just trying to trap me
because she wanted to be with you she
slept with one of my friends a day after
I had sex with her maybe he's the father
she's a young girl that slept with too
many gods now she's got a situation on
her hands not my fault the baby was
deceived the whole month and a half
before she was even with me so I know it
can't be mine I won't buy something for
a baby that is not mine here's Diamond
everybody
[Applause]
you admit you know the condom went off
it kind of came off at any point of time
that's because she took it off
[Applause]
like what one
that baby look like you
yeah
anything that the baby would be it would
be the hair or the nose and other than
that there was nothing else on that baby
that looks like me she had to drop out
of school
you feel bad about that no no he don't
care I don't care
you're still a little boy
so what you're saying is she was messing
around with other people at the same
time I couldn't even tell you how many
people more how do you know
[Applause]
when it comes to three month old
Christiana Diamond you are not
[Applause]
away
oh
where are you going it's a running fool
huh
I'm not the father
[Music]
with diamond Diamond's not the dance
oh my goodness this is so cool everyone
this is Brad welcome Brad
now
Brad says that this woman named Amanda
has pounced on his heart more times than
he can count
he lost his virginity to her
they were once in love until
she sent naked pictures of herself to
several men
[Applause]
including one of his best friends
Amanda claims that Cameron her son
belongs to Brad
but Brad
fears he will be crushed once again when
the DNA test proves he's not Cameron's
death
w-h-o-r-e that's the word used to
describe a manner she sent naked
pictures to my best friend cheated on me
and all I did was give my heart to her
and she ripped it out of my chest and
stepped all over it
this baby he would have been a miracle
baby I was so happy that I could
actually know that I could have children
and then she told me that it could be
another man's baby and I just broke my
heart I missed it for Christmas his
first Halloween all these other people
get a hold of him and I don't the most
important person in his life I thought
on Facebook that she was giving birth to
my son I missed it completely how can I
ever replace that remember I'm never
going to be able to do that I just don't
I don't know I want to be his daddy
you were in love with this woman I was I
loved her dearly
I loved her with all my heart boy what'd
you do
she cheated on me
and I know she sent pictures to my best
friend of her naked man
I never understood why she never gave me
a reason you know who has those pictures
[Applause]
obviously ladies and gentlemen we have
been hearing from Lily he is Brad's
mother now you have never met this child
have you I've never met a memorial I've
never gotten to hold him in my arms
I haven't gotten what's that
this is a tour I want him to have
something
that is from his dad
this is what you had to say Breaking My
Heart the brass playing the victim I
never did anything wrong I never cheated
on him I'm sick and tired of him telling
lies but I just want to cheated on me he
needs to stop playing fingers and
accusing me of doing it when I told Brad
I was pregnant he didn't want anything
to do with me he blocked me off of
Facebook and he turned his back on me
his mom really makes me mad she needs to
learn how to mind her own business and
stay out of bars he's a brown man needs
to take care of his own problems I
believe that Brad is about their baby
camera and I will prove it today
all right Amanda here's Amanda
[Applause]
shut up
did you tell him in the beginning he
wasn't the phone at the beginning yes I
had to tell him that because you know
when me and him broke up you know I went
with another guy you know and you didn't
break up I got rid of your ass
foreign
I want to give Amanda a fair Shake here
everyone is he the father of this child
I believe he is the father of my child
if he's the father he has a right to be
in this child yeah and I want if he is
the father I want him to be part of the
kid's life damn straight I'm going to be
part of his life
I'm going to take care of him my father
is
you want to be the father Yes I do in
the case of six-month-old Cameron Brad
you are not
[Applause]
a little
on my own business we'll be glad to help
you if you want us to if you want to
seek another because I know who the
father is you know if it's not him then
it's the other guy that's the only one
other person I've been with thank you
look you say you have a dream life
you go live it you love it honey you
don't have to do it and save that for
them thank God you don't have to deal
with her everybody Welcome Sierra
now Sierra
Sierra has a beautiful three-month-old
son Caden
see Sierra says
this man Mario was ready to step up
admit he was the father and take care of
Caden until his meddling mother Yvette
put the brakes on
you see even Yvette says about herself
I'm a CIA agent
and she claims to have had Sierra's
house under surveillance
and she claims that guess what Sierra's
house was like a revolving door with men
coming in and going out people coming in
so that there's no way that her son
fathered this baby so you think it's
Yvette Yvette is the only reason that
Mario is denying this child yes Murray
it's her she needs to mind her business
let him be a man
Daddy
[Applause]
and be a man she's worried about the
money she's money home one money
[Applause]
baby saying that he's the father she
won't be getting no more his money
[Applause]
don't worry about
sleeping
[Applause]
don't worry about it okay does he seen
the baby he's thinking once since he's
been born
[Applause]
well guess what come on this is what
Mario and his mom Yvette had to say
watch I don't need Maury I don't need a
doctor I don't need a DNA test to prove
that I'm not father Sierra's baby I know
this baby's not mine and so does my
mother I asked another class to see from
Sierra I see men's going in and out all
the time her house was just like a
Reviving door this is Sierra's fault not
my mother's my mom was just telling me
what's really going on she invited me
over one night to watch a movie and the
next thing I know I was in her bed I see
one is my son's mind I don't know what
that baby looks like but I know he's
definitely not my son's baby Sierra
wants me in her life because she knows
that I'm a good guy but she's not about
the ruin my life because of her mistakes
[Applause]
why are you here
does that baby look like anybody in your
family it's not
I don't know who it looks like Mario
nice to see you too much pretty tough
huh
you're in the middle of this no I didn't
in the middle I ain't got nothing to do
with this but she probably
[Applause]
first of all father of that child you'll
take out right yeah I have to right and
by the way Yvette if your son is the
father of that child you would welcome
your grandbaby wouldn't I have no
problem with that more let me just
put it out here right okay okay number
one because she said we shouldn't even
be sitting here why because she had
foreign
[Music]
is
you never said
because I know I know
you know about being a family I know
that if this is your child you'll help
with this of course
here we go
when it comes to three month old Kaden
Mario you are not
[Applause]
thank you